{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 14x - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5/3", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (3/5)x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 10x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 9x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3/10)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (3/10)x + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5/13", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-13/5)x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 10x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 5x - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -x - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (2/3)x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 2x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 2x + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(14/9)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (14/9)x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -11x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 11x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -9x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 2x + 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-14/13)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-14/13)x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7/9)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (7/9)x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5/11", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-11/5)x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/5", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 5x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -13x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13/9", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (9/13)x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-7/11)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-7/11)x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -10x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-13/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (2/13)x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 8x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-11/2)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-11/2)x - 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-10/3)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-10/3)x - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12/7", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-7/12)x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7/8", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-8/7)x + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/7", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -7x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 11x - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 7x + 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/4", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 4x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2/5", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (5/2)x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -5x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/12", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -12x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/6", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 6x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d x - 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 5x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/4", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -4x - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -5x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 7x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4/7)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-4/7)x - 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(13/12)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (13/12)x - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 2x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2/5", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (5/2)x + 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-14", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -14x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -10x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7/5)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (7/5)x - 10", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6/11)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (6/11)x - 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-7/12)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-7/12)x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 2x - 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-11", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -11x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/3", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -3x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 10x - 11", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15/7", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (7/15)x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -10x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8/15", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-15/8)x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/12", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 12x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 5x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (1/15)x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-3/2)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-3/2)x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 3x - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/6", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 6x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/2", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -2x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7/3", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-3/7)x - 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(7/4)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (7/4)x + 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(5/2)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (5/2)x + 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3/7", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-7/3)x - 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 4x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-10/3)x - 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -x - 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d -7x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15/4", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-4/15)x - 13", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2/3)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-2/3)x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 13x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 2x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/15", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d -15x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 6x - 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-4/5)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-4/5)x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1/6", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d 6x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d x + 12", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14/15", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-15/14)x + 15", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11/10", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-10/11)x + 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 5x + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9/8", "explanation": "The slope of a perpendicular line is the negative reciprical of the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line perpendicular to this line:\n y \u003d (-8/9)x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 11x + 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 13x + 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d 4x - 14", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(-2/13)", "explanation": "The slope of a parallel line is the same the slope of the given line.", "question": "Find the slope of a line parallel to this line:\n y \u003d (-2/13)x + 11", "type": "text"}
]}